Finding Aid for Satakunta Region immigrant letters, 1880-1964
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Merikarvia, letters to
  - Toivo Lehtinen
    - from: Karl Virtanen. Mass., 1949-1950; 5 items (Reel 15)
    - from: Lempi Ylinen. Minn., 1950-1951; 5 items (Reel 15)
    - from: Urho Ylinen. Minn., 1951; 3 items (Reel 15)
    - from: Villjam Ylinen. Minn., 1950-1957; 4 items (Reel 15)
    - from: Albert Ylinen. Ont., 1952; 3 items (Reel 15)
    - from: Frans Ylinen. Minn., 1950-1951; 2 items (Reel 15)
  - Erik Peräla
    - from: Oskar Perala.
      - Minn., 1902; 1 items (Reel 15)
      - Ironwood, Mich., 1908; 1 items (Reel 15)
  - Paavo Heikkilä
    - from: Heikki Mikkola. Ohio, 1893; 2 items (Reel 15)
  - Wilhelmiina Lönnberg
    - from: unnamed. Mass., 1893; 1 items (Reel 15)
    - from Lydia Gronberg.
      - Stambaugh, Mich., 1900-1901; 2 items (Reel 15)
      - Con.,1904-1905, 2 items (Reel 15)
  - Wilhelmiina Lönnberg
    - from: Amanda Osterby. Mansfield, Mich., 1905; 2 items (Reel 15)
    - from: unnamed. Stambaugh, Mich., 1900; 1 items (Reel 15)
    - from Lydia Lonnberg. Iron Mountain, Mich., undated; 1 items (Reel 15)
    - from: Ellen Lonnberg. Conn., undated; 1 items (Reel 15)
    - from: unnamed.Conn., undated; 4 items (Reel 15)
    - from: unnamed. Mass., 1904; 2 items (Reel 15)
  - Gustaf Lönnberg
    - from: Vaino Lonnberg. Oregon., 1905; 4 items (Reel 15)
  - Paavo Lönnberg
    - from: Sven Lonnberg
      - Stambaugh, Mich., 1899; 1 items (Reel 15)
      - Oregon., 1904; 1 items (Reel 15)
  - Kustaa Louhi
    - from: Sven Lonnberg. Ore., 1941-1950; 32 items (Reel 15)
    - from: Lydia Andersson. Conn., 1948-1953; 3 items (Reel 15)
    - from: Toivo Osterby. Oregon., 1941-1959; 7 items (Reel 15)
    - from: Helli Louhi. N.Y., Ore., 1948-1951; 23 items (Reel 15)
  - Martta Meura
    - from: Iisakki Vanhatalo. Minn., 1897; 1 items (Reel 15)
    - from: Emilia Kallio. Crystal Falls, Mich., 1903; 2 items (Reel 15)
  - Jenni Hankomaa
    - from: Viljan Virta. Crystal Falls, Mich., 1951; 1 items (Reel 15)
  - Heimo Meura
    - from: V.J. Laaksonen. B.C., 1947-1957; 24 items (Reel 15)
  - Lauri Vilen
    - from: Hilda Kainulainen. Marquette, Mich., 1946; 3 items (Reel 15)
  - T. Innola
    - from: V.J. Laaksonen. B.C.:, 1954-1958; 14 items (Reel 15)
  - Linda Kivinen
    - from: Oskari Mattila. Rock, Mich., 1952; 1 items (Reel 15)
  - Herman Törmä
    - from: Juho Ranta. Wash., 1952-1958; 4 items (Reel 15)
    - from: Lempi Sjoholm. N.Y., 1958-1961; 3 items (Reel 15)
  - Lyydia Vanhatalo
    - from: Anna Hemp. Calif., 1945-1963; 23 items (Reel 15)
  - Hulda Heikkil
    - from: Sandra Johansson. Mass., Ill., 1921-1961; 2 items (Reel 15)
  - Miina Järvinen
    - from: Iida Järvi. Ill., 1963; 4 items (Reel 15)
  - Amalia Luomansuu
    - from: Anselmi Neva.
      - Boston, Mich., Demmon, Mich., Green, Mich., 1906-1919; 3 items (Reel 15)
      - Minn., undated; 1 items (Reel 15)
      - Ontonagon, Mich., 1930; 1 items (Reel 15)
      - Minn. (l item), 1931 (Reel 15)
  - Jalmari Luomansuu
    - from: Arttur Vesa. Green, Mich., 1920-1923; 6 items (Reel 15)
  - Antti Myllykallio
    - from: H. Saari. Ont., 1958; 17 items (Reel 15)
  - Hanna Nurmi
    - from: Aino Porre. Mont., 1958-1961; 4 items (Reel 15)
    - from: Jenny Ranta. Calif., 1957-1963; 11 items (Reel 15)
  - Selma Näsi
    - from: Martin Wirtanen. Mass., 1950-1964; 3 items (Reel 15)
    - from: Ida Jarvin. Ill., 1956; 2 items (Reel 15)
    - from: Saima Woodward. Mass., 1961-1964; 4 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Hilja Rantala. Ont., 1963-1964; 7 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Ellen Lindman. Minn., 1962; 2 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Toivo Mannerhaimo. Australia, undated; 6 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Silmu Salmio. Minn., 1962-1963; 2 items (Reel 16)
  - Emilia Lahti
    - from: Lempi Seppanen.
      - Rock, Mich., 1961; 3 items (Reel 16)
      - Arizona, 1963; 2 items (Reel 16)
      - Rock, Mich., 1963; 3 items (Reel 16)
      - Arizona, 1963-1964; 5 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Olga Hull. Detroit, Mich., 1964; 2 items (Reel 16)
  - Jussi Mäkipuro
    - from: Vihtori Hemp. Calif., 1958; 1 items (Reel 16)
  - Elli Perlkannu
    - from: Frank Maki. Crystal Falls, Mich., 1959; 1 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Fanny Mathen. Crystal Falls, Mich., 1960; 1 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Tyyne Pfuffer
      - Crystal Falls, Mich., 1963; 1 items (Reel 16)
      - Ill., 1963; 1 items (Reel 16)
  - Fiina Lähteenmäki
    - from: Alma Rintamaki. Crystal Falls, Mich., 1947; 1 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Alma Talo. Negaunee, Mich., 1947; 1 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Johan Lahteenmaki. Utah, 1909; 1 items (Reel 16)
  - Kalle Vanhatalo
    - from: Vihtori Hemp. Cal., 1947-1948; 2 items (Reel 16)
  - Katri Lähteenmäki
    - from: Nestor Kallioinen. Negaunee, Mich.1940-1945 (.2 items) (Reel 16)
    - from: Hanna Nelson. Munising, Mich., 1955; 6 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Alma Kallioinen. Negaunee, Mich., 1946-1959; 15 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Frans Kallioinen. Negaunee, Mich., 1940-1963; 2 items (Reel 16)
    - from: E. Wahl. Ont., 1964; 2 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Nestor Kallioinen. Negaunee, Mich., 1958; 1 items (Reel 16)
  - Helmi Mäkipuro
    - from: Anna Hemp. Calif., 1962; 1 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Helmi Kallio. Conn., Fla., 1959-1964; 2 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Eila Makipuro. N.Y., 1962; 2 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Hannu Makipuro. Conn., 1961; 1 items (Reel 16)
  - Kaisa Toivonen
    - from: Tenny Juhola. Crystal Falls, Mich., 1958-1963; 5 items (Reel 16)
  - Oiva Fredrikson
    - from: Wiljam Mikkelson. N.Y., 1936-1939; 4 items (Reel 16)
  - Eelis Haanpää
    - from: Matti Haanpaa. Bessemer, Mich., Ironwood, Mich., 1953-1954; 3 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Matti Haanpaa. Bessemer, Mich., 1947-1952; 10 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Walfred Haanpaa. Detroit, Mich., 1949-1950; 3 items (Reel 16)
  - Esko Haanpää
    - from: Walfred Haanpaa. Detroit, Mich., Mt. Clemens, Mi., 1954-1957; 2 items (Reel 16)
  - Paavo Koskilahti
    - from: Alina Back. Minn., 1922-1946; 3 items (Reel 16)
  - O. Naavala
    - from: Miina Friberg. Mass., 1937; 2 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Laura Klein. Mass., 1963; 1 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Wiljam Mikkelson. N.Y., 1940; 1 items (Reel 16)
    - from: kViljam Mikkelson. N.Y., 1946; 1 items (Reel 16)
  - Ottilia Rantamäki
    - from: Charles Sandberg. Minn., 1963; 2 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Hilja Hill. Wash., 1961-1963; 4 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Alise Hannula. N.Y., 1960-1963; 4 items (Reel 16)
  - Leo Salokanto
    - from: Mina Hill. Minn., 1955-1969; 7 items (Reel 16)
  - Eine Vähätalo
    - from: Frans Laine. L'Anse, Mich., 1950-1957; 4 items (Reel 16)
  - Hilja Vähätalo
    - from: Frans Laine. L'Anse, Mich., 1946-1950; 5 items (Reel 16)
  - Senja Nikaniemi
    - from: Marja Pettersson. Wash., 1946; 1 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Ida Lattu. Calif., 1961-1963; 4 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Hilda Mackie. B.C.:, 1959-1963; 5 items (Reel 16)
  - Betty Rata
    - from: Hilja Stenberg. Ohio, 1949-1953; 5 items (Reel 16)
  - Eelis Vuorisalo
    - from: Anna Backlund. Crystal Falls, Mich., 1946-1961; 4 items (Reel 16)
  - Helmi Metsänurmi
    - from: Jalmari Heikkilä, N.H., 1952; 1 items (Reel 16)
  - Lauri Metsänurmi
    - from: Uuno Norlund. Minn., 1964; 1 items (Reel 16)
  - Helmi Metsänurmi
    - from: Anna Heikkila. N.H., 1952-1956; 2 items (Reel 16)
  - Lauri Metsänurmi
    - from: Konsta Westerlund. Minn., 1961; 1 items (Reel 16)
  - Jenny Haanpää
    - from: Viljami Haanpaa. Crystal Falls, Mich., 1937; 2 items (Reel 16)
  - Auno Lehto
    - from: Aino Borre. Mont., 1959-1963; 3 items (Reel 16)
  - Kaisa Mikkola
    - from: Edla Ahola. Fla., 1957-1961; 2 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Fanni Jarvi. Cal., 1955-1963; 2 items (Reel 16)
  - Jalmari Makitalo
    - from: Oskar Stengard. Wis., 1940-1946; 2 items (Reel 16)
  - Albert Raunela
    - from: Elina Rajaniemi. N.Y., Mass., Wis., 1947-1961; 23 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Jalmari Salonen. Mass., 1959; 1 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Elli Skogman. Cal., 1959; 1 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Mauno Raunela. Mass., 1955-1969; 8 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Fanni Miettinen. N.D., 1934; 1 items (Reel 16)
  - Viljo Vuorisalo
    - from: Hanna Alenius. Stambaugh, Mich., 1946; 1 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Johan Rosenberg. Grayling, Mich., 1939-1958; 2 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Anna Vanhala. Detroit, Mich., 1961; 4 items (Reel 16)
  - Väinö Aittomäki
    - from: Ida Johansson., undated; 1 items (Reel 16)
  - Helmi Jyminä
    - from: Fanni Juhola. Crystal Falls, Mich., 1957; 1 items (Reel 16)
  - Aini Laitinen
    - from: Paavo Uusitalo. Cal., 1959-1963; 3 items (Reel 16)
  - Heikki Laitinen
    - from: Hilda Uusitalo. Cal., 1963; 1 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Paavo Uusitalo
      - Calif., 1964; 1 items (Reel 16)
      - Detroit, Mich., 1959; 1 items (Reel 16)
  - Sandra Rantala
    - from: Fanny Mathens. Crystal Falls, Mich. (Reel 16)
    - from: unnamed. Crystal Falls, Mich., 1958; 2 items (Reel 16)
  - Hilja Riihiaho
    - from: J. Walkama. Wash., 1920; 1 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Selma Walkama. Wash., 1914-1917; 2 items (Reel 16)
  - Betty Setälä
    - from: Martta Setala., 1960-1963; 3 items (Reel 16)
  - Kaisu Toivonen
    - from: Hilma Pollari. Crystal Falls, Mich., Kingsford, Mich., 1958-1963; 2 items (Reel 16)
  - Aarne Uusitalo
    - from: Paavo Uusitalo. Cal., 1952-1964; 8 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Paavo Uusitalo. Calif., 1961; 1 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Paavo Uusitalo. Calif., 1964; 2 items (Reel 16)
  - Helmi Uusitalo
    - from: Paavo Uusitalo. Calif., 1963-1964; 3 items (Reel 16)
  - Telmi Uusitalo
    - from: Hilda Hognesback. Ont. (l items), 1962 (Reel 16)
  - Hilja Uusitalo
    - from: Paavo Uusitalo. Calif., 1957-1961; 8 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Katri Koski. N.Y., Fla., 1957-1959; 4 items (Reel 16)
  - Väinö Vainio
    - from: E. Mannig. N.Y., 1964; 1 items (Reel 16)
  - Hanna Vuorela
    - from: Aini Salo. Conn. (l items), 1962 (Reel 16)
  - Miina Aittamäki
    - from: Arvid Maki. Iron River, Mich., 1956; 2 items (Reel 16)
  - Hanna Alho
    - from: Fanny Juhola. Crystal Falls, Mich., 1958; 1 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Hilma Laitinen. Negaunee, Mich.1953-1958, 7 items (Reel 16)
  - Marja Josefiina Koivunen
    - from: Ida Aalto. Calif., 1949-1951; 3 items (Reel 16)
  - Taisto Korpela
    - from: Alma Niemi. N.Y., 1961; 3 items (Reel 16)
  - Sandra Santavuori
    - from: Ida Aalto. Calif., 1951-1952; 2 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Emilia Johansson. Cal., 1946-1963; 3 items (Reel 16)
  - Hulda Siirtonen
    - from: Ida Aalto. Calif., 1946; 1 items (Reel 16)
    - from: Albert Lindman. Minn., 1953; 1 items (Reel 16)
  - Ida Aavakari
    - from: Aali Lehtonen. Minn., 1952-1962; 13 items (Reel 16)
  - Elsa Kalaranta
    - from: Aini Kinnunen. Calif., 1961-1964; 3 items (Reel 17)
  - Helmi Fagerroos
    - from: Aini Luke. Minn., 1953; 1 items (Reel 17)
    - from: Gunnar Viikinsalo. Minn., 1953; 1 items (Reel 17)
  - Ida Haapala
    - from: Frans Koskiranta. Wis., 1951; 1 items (Reel 17)
    - from: Eva Nieminen. B.C.:, 1960-1964; 7 items (Reel 17)
  - Lauri Haapaniemi
    - from: Vaino Niemi. Minn., 1928; 2 items (Reel 17)
  - Aili Lammi
    - from: John Pelli. Wash., 1955-1963; 5 items (Reel 17)
    - from: Aino Marley. Alta., 1951-1963; 8 items (Reel 17)
  - Anni Lehto
    - from: Jenny Ranta. Calif., 1962-1963; 6 items (Reel 17)
  - Väinö Mattila
    - from: Ida Vanhajuhola. Calif., Fla., 1962-1964; 8 items (Reel 17)
  - Helli Ojala
    - from: Katri Nikkila. Fla., 1961-1962; 2 items (Reel 17)
  - Pentti Ojala
    - from: Frans Koskinen. Account book and diary. Finland (l items), 1964 (Reel 17)
  - Vihtori Ojala
    - from: Elsa Johnson. N.Y., 1961; 1 items (Reel 17)
  - Aili Pohjola
    - from: Jenny Pohjola. Minn., 1962-1964; 3 items (Reel 17)
    - from: Edith Haapala. Cal., 1961; 1 items (Reel 17)
    - from: Fanny Holmbo. Calif., 1961; 11 items (Reel 17)
  - Maria Rantala
    - from: Maria Lahti. Crystal Falls, Mich., Iron River, Mich., 1961-1963; 3 items (Reel 17)
    - from: Paavo Posti. B.C.:, 1955-1963; 5 items (Reel 17)
  - Salme Salmi
    - from: Edith Lahtinen. Ont., 1958-1962; 3 items (Reel 17)
  - Sofia Slutbacka
    - from: Juho Slutback. Minn., 1914-1923; 8 items (Reel 17)
  - Hanna Vanhatalo
    - from: Aili Lahtinen. Minn., 1949; 8 items (Reel 17)
    - from: Aili Luoma. Minn., 1952-1961; 18 items (Reel 17)
  - Veikko Vähgtalo
    - from: Johan Maki. Ont., 1956-1964; 5 items (Reel 17)
  - Lauri Vihervuori
    - from: Aini Salo. Conn., 1956-1964; 4 items (Reel 17)
  - Paul Vuorenmaa
    - from: Aini Sainio. Cal., 1934; 1 items (Reel 17)
  - Maija Vuori
    - from: Vaino Salo. Minn., 1956-1964; 3 items (Reel 17)
  - Alma Koskinen
    - from: Elsie Johnson. N.Y., 1937-1946; 4 items (Reel 17)
  - Eino Mattila
    - from: Martti Marttila. Minn., 1949-1962; 3 items (Reel 17)
  - Hilkka Poikkeus
    - from: Oskar Joensuu. Minn., 1960-1962; 12 items (Reel 17)
  - Alma Koskinen
    - from: Frans Koski. N.Y., 1928-1945; 3 items (Reel 17)
  - Hanna Palomäki
    - from: Katri Koski. N.Y., 1950-1954; 18 items (Reel 17)
  - Lyydi Toivonen
    - from: Arvo Toivonen., 1916; 2 items (Reel 17)
  - Helmi Uusimäki
    - from: Maria Lahti. Crystal Falls, Mich., 1961-1963; 2 items (Reel 17)
  - Hugo Bondfolk
    - from: Elsa Kosola. Ont., 1960-1961; 2 items (Reel 17)
    - from: Hugo Bondfolk. 1 diary (in Swedish), 1931 (Reel 17)
  - Jalmari Haanpää
    - from: Kalle Karjala. Mont., 1958-1963; 5 items (Reel 17)
  - Hilma Järvelä
    - from: Hulda Saari. Ont., 1945-1956; 37 items (Reel 17)
  - Aini Kaihe
    - from: Aili Lehto. Minn., 1964; 1 items (Reel 17)
  - Vihtori Karumäki
    - from: Veikko Karumaki. Australia, 1964; 3 items (Reel 17)
  - Selma Mahlamäki
    - from: Aili Honkanen. Detroit, Mich., 1964; 2 items (Reel 17)
  - Antti Myllykallio
    - from: Ida Sidar. Fla., 1962-1964; 2 items (Reel 17)
  - Ella Mäntylahti
    - from Lydia West. Ont., 1946-1953; 5 items (Reel 17)
    - from: Johan Maki. Ont., 1955; 1 items (Reel 17)
    - from: Robert West. Ont. (l items), 1947 (Reel 17)
  - Elin Rantala
    - from: Kaisa Johnson. Ont., 1961-1963; 3 items (Reel 17)
  - Nestori Rajala
    - from: Anton Ranta. Bear Lake, Mich., 1947; 1 items (Reel 17)
  - Laimi Ruohonen
    - from: Hanna McDaniel. S.D., 1961-1963; 3 items (Reel 17)
  - Mauno Salminen
    - from: H. Laine. Minn., 1954-1962; 3 items (Reel 17)
  - Heikki Voihinen
    - from: Else Gleason. Ishpeming, Mich., 1962; 1 items (Reel 17)
    - from: Fanni Juhola. Crystal Falls, Mich., 1961-1963; 5 items (Reel 17)
  - Martta Virtanen
    - from: Fiina Lahnakoski. Minn., 1940; 1 items (Reel 17)
    - from: Kalle Virtanen. Mass., 1938; 1 items (Reel 17)
  - Senja Salminen
    - from: Vaino Marjamaki. B.C.:, 1959-1964; 8 items (Reel 17)
  - Lauri Järvenpää
    - from: Aarne Jarvi. N.Y., Fla., 1951-1955; 14 items (Reel 17)
    - from: Aino Jarvi. Ont., Minn., N.Y., Fla., 1952-1955; 18 items (Reel 17)
  - Eelin Tiittanen
    - from: Olga Suominen. Wis., 1951-1952; 14 items (Reel 17)
    - from: Olga Suominen. Wis., 1952-1953; 14 items (Reel 18)
  - Reino Mäkinen
    - from: N.Y., 1950-1951; 4 items (Reel 18)
  - Hilma Salonen
    - from: Jenni Salonen. Ont., 1962-1964; 9 items (Reel 18)
  - Emilia Veirtola
    - from: Urho Juhola. Ont., 1956-1957; 2 items (Reel 18)
  - Eliina Väliluoma
    - from: Martta Attard. N.Y., 1951-1964; 31 items (Reel 18)
  - Aune Jakola
    - from: Raakel Vanhala
      - Ont., 1923; 2 items (Reel 18)
      - Pelkie, Mich., Alston, Mich., Nisula, Mich. Detroit, Mich., Hancock, Mich., Houghton,. Mich., Livonia, Mich., 1946-1969; 40 items (Reel 18)
  - Hilma Katajamäki
    - from: Maria Lahti
      - Crystal Falls, Mich., 1962; 1 items (Reel 18)
      - Mass., 1963; 1 items (Reel 18)
      - Iron River, Mich., 1963; 1 items (Reel 18)
  - Kaisa Koivula
    - from: Eeva Lahtinen. N.Y., Mass., 1939; 6 items (Reel 18)
  - Hanna Kortessalo
    - from: Lempi Ranta. Detroit, Mich., 1963-1964; 4 items (Reel 18)
  - Aili Salokanto
    - from: Alma Nelsson. Mass., 1958; 1 items (Reel 18)
  - Robert Vähätalo
    - from: Robert West. Ont., 1947-1948; 3 items (Reel 18)
  - Paavo Varjosuo
    - from: Juho Haggroth. Alta., 1946-1953; 18 items (Reel 18)
  - Arvo Kalliovuo
    - from: Frans Makinen. Fla., 1964; 4 items (Reel 18)
  - Saima Pihlajamäki
    - from: Irene Hama. Mass., 1953-1961; 4 items (Reel 18)
  - Irja Pohjanlehto
    - from: Emilia Lahti. Carlshend, Mich., Dukes, Mich., 1947-1951; 11 items (Reel 18)
  - Suoma Salrinen
    - from: Milja Lahti. Skandia, Mich., 1947; 7 items (Reel 18)
  - Laimi Silmu
    - from: Irene Holma. Mass., 1956-1961; 4 items (Reel 18)
  - Niilo Syrjäsalo
    - from: Arvo Rosenholm. B.C.:, 1929-1945; 6 items (Reel 18)
  - Vieno Vuorela
    - from: Ella Johansson. Ont., Fla, 1961-1964; 4 items (Reel 18)
  - Ellen Vähätalo
    - from: Sulo West. Ont., 1946-1953; 5 items (Reel 18)
  - Reino Vähätalo
    - from: Johan Maki. Ont., 1957-1959; 2 items (Reel 18)
  - Robert Vähätalo
    - from: Johan Maki. Ont., 1935-1955; 4 items (Reel 18)
  - Reino Vähätalo
    - from: Sulo West. Ont., 1946-1947; 2 items (Reel 18)
  - Aali Rikalainen
    - from: Aino Salonen. N.Y., 1963; 1 items (Reel 18)
  - Anna-Liisa Valtonen
    - from: Hilda Rajala. Ont., 1957; 1 items (Reel 18)
  - Vihtori Mäkinen
    - from: Margit Mäkinen. Ont., Fla., 1945; 10 items (Reel 18)
  - Hilda Kivistö
    - from: R. Mills. Ont., Alta., 1952-1961; 3 items (Reel 18)
  - Anna-Liisa Valtonen
    - from: Leena Nieminen., 1957; 1 items (Reel 18)
  - Jussi Atvio
    - from: Randy Erikson. Ore., 1962; 3 items (Reel 18)
  - Unknown Recipient
    - from: Toivo Osterby., undated; 2 items (Reel 18)
  - Irene Alho
    - from: Mildred Wiggerth. Ann Arbor, Mich., Chelsea, Mich. Roseville, Mich., 1949-1958; 9 items (Reel 18)
  - Hilja Atvio
    - from: Elle Erikson. Oregon., 1959-1961; 33 items (Reel 18)
  - Marjatta Etumäki
    - from: Bonnie Maki. Stambaugh, Mich., 1958; 1 items (Reel 18)
  - Randolph Gustafson
    - from: Arvo Uusiheikkila. Iron River, Mich., 1953-1959; 11 items (Reel 18)
  - Annikki Jalava
    - from: E. Smith. Fla., 1961; 1 items (Reel 18)
  - Sanna-Liisa Kivelä
    - from: D. Pointon. B.C.:, 1964; 1 items (Reel 18)
  - Linda Kivinen
    - from: Helmi Mattila. Ill., 1952-1963; 8 items (Reel 18)
  - Aimo Myllymäki
    - from: Helen Maki. N.J., Fla., 1953-1961; 12 items (Reel 18)
  - Saima Pihlajamäki
    - from: Taisto Pihlajamaki. Mass., 1960-1961; 3 items (Reel 18)
  - J. O. Rikalainen
    - from: Herbert Hoover. D.C., 1938; 1 items (Reel 18)
- Metsämaa, letters to
  - Sofia Sainio
    - from: Alfred Maki. Calif., 1946-1962; 3 items (Reel 18)
  - Hilma Lehtinen
    - from: Alma Erickson. Calif., 1950-1961; 10 items (Reel 18)
  - Naimi Helin
    - from: Suoma Kantonen. Mass., 1949-1956; 2 items (Reel 18)
  - Aleksi Saarinen
    - from: John Saari. Alta., 1945-1964; 2 items (Reel 18)
  - Aino Mikkola
    - from: Mandi Levo. Minn., 1961; 8 items (Reel 18)
  - Mikko Mäki
    - from: Aina Jutila., undated; 2 items (Reel 18)
  - Oskari Tervasmäki
    - from: Kalle Tervasmaki. Minn., 1925-1949; 10 items (Reel 18)
  - Unto Rinne
    - from: Tyyne Kilter., 1949; 1 items (Reel 18)
    - from: Lempi Korpela. N.Y., 1926; 1 items (Reel 18)
  - Tyyne Sorri
    - from: Lyydia Bradley. Fla., 1960-1962; 4 items (Reel 18)
  - Olga Arola
    - from: Elna Arola. N.Y., 1930; 6 items (Reel 18)
  - Hilja Hokka
    - from: Naima Saarinen. Calif., 1946-1964; 9 items (Reel 18)
  - Martta Maki
    - from: Walma Wiitasalo. Wash., 1950-1953; 2 items (Reel 18)
  - Saima Jalasjoki
    - from: Viljo Orell. N.Y., 1937; 1 items (Reel 18)
    - from: Arttu Orell. Maine, 1936; 1 items (Reel 18)
  - Enni Ojalainen
    - from: Selma Ojalainen. B.C., Ont., 1960-1964; 5 items (Reel 18)
  - Lauri Laakso
    - from: Suoma Kala, Fannie Jarvi. Calif., Wis., 1947-1964; 20 items (Reel 18)
- Mouhijärvi, letters to
  - Anna Ahola
    - from: Hilda Mickelson. Calif., 1961; 1 items (Reel 19)
  - Tilda Huuppo
    - from: Martti Iikkila. photos, 2 items (Reel 19)
  - Martta Mikkola
    - from: Hilda Mikkola. Ill., Wis., Fla., 1933-1964; 6 items (Reel 19)
  - Frans Mikkola
    - from Lauri Mikkola. B.C., 1960-1962; 5 items (Reel 19)
- Noormarkku, letters to
  - Anni Hatanpää
    - from: Ida Saukko. Cal., 1959; 1 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Emil Koivisto. Mass., 1961; 1 items (Reel 19)
  - Hilda Seppä
    - from: Sanni Wesa. Detroit, Mich., 1941-1949; 16 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Johanna Aalto. Mass., 1947-1963; 7 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Hilda Waak. Rock, Mich., 1953-1954; 3 items (Reel 19)
  - Valtter Tuomisalo
    - from: Tilda Kuoppala. Ill., 1952; 1 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Jussi Lammi. Escanaba, Mich., 1948; 1 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Suoma Wikman. Calif., 1950; 3 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Laimi Hasu. Calif., 1954; 1 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Vaino Tuomisalo. Ont., 1955-1963; 5 items (Reel 19)
  - Viktor Aalto
    - from: Rikhard Makela. Minn., 1962; 1 items (Reel 19)
  - Eeva Alajärvi
    - from: Kustaava Keiju. Ont., 1939-1957; 5 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Aino Vuorinen. Mass., Fla., 1962-1964; 3 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Saima Hendriksson. Wash., 1962-1963; 2 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Jalmari Vanhatalo. B.C.:, 1953-1962; 8 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Lempi Maattanen. N.Y., 1960-1964; 3 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Ilma Auranen. Ont., 1952-1963; 7 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Aune Pulkkinen. Wis., N.Y., 1949-1951 (Reel 19)
  - Hilma Kartano
    - from: Jenny Metsala. Fla., 1956; 1 items (Reel 19)
  - Elle Koskinen
    - from: Betty Vainio. Negaunee, Mich., 1947-1969; 2 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Lauri Lahti. Ironwood, Mich., 1930s (Reel 19)
  - Frans Mäkinen
    - from: John Karvonen. Idaho, 1949-1961; 3 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Robert Maki. Ont., 1937-1952; 5 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Jack Koski. Ont., 1936; 1 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Antero Makinen. Ont., 1945-1963; 3 items (Reel 19)
  - Martta Mäkinen
    - from: Venneri Vahekoski. Nevada, 1939; 1 items (Reel 19)
  - Juho Mäkitalo
    - from: Oskar Maki. Fla., undated; 1 items (Reel 19)
  - Anna-Liisa Korkeakoski
    - from: Iida Maki. Marquette, Mich., 1962-1963; 3 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Olga Matt. Marquette, Mich., 1963; 1 items (Reel 19)
  - Bertta Roslöf
    - from: Ivar Niemi. Mass., 1956; 1 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Johan Vallin. Calif., 1961; 4 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Paavo Wesslin. Ont., 1926-1962; 14 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Ralph Delarye. Negaunee, Mich., 1946-1948; 2 items (Reel 19)
    - from: Vaino Kuivinen
      - Ohio, 1929; 1 items (Reel 19)
      - Ishpeming, Mich., 1932; 1 items (Reel 19)
  - Eeva Korpela
    - from: Helvi Kaasalainen. Ont., 1955; 1 items (Reel 19)
- Parkano, letters to
  - Elina Nieminen
    - from: Signe Danielson. Minn., 1951-1962; 17 items (Reel 19)
  - Frans Koskela
    - from: Otto Koskela. Mass, Mich., Sault Ste. Marie, Mich., 1946-1955; 34 items (Reel 19)
  - Arvid Länsimäki
    - from: Ville Luoma. Ont., 1946; 14 items (Reel 19)
  - Rauha Rantaniemi
    - from: Eliina Koskinen. Minn., Ont., 1964; 5 items (Reel 19)
  - Aleksandra VuorenpAd
    - from: Hilja Wiiki. Minn., 1962-1964 (Reel 19)
  - Aini Rintamäki
    - from: Fiina Wuori. Minn., 1962; 1 items (Reel 19)
  - Martta Joensuu
    - from: Lempi Pajala. Minn., 1951-1956; 2 items (Reel 19)
  - Kyllikki Kallio
    - from: Signe Tuomi. Minn., 1963-1964; 11 items (Reel 19)
  - Lempi Keskinen
    - from: Niilo Palmi. Minn., 1956; 1 items (Reel 19)
  - Aksa Koivunen
    - from:. N.H., Minn., 1938-1952; 16 items (Reel 19)
  - Manta Kuivanen
    - from: Hilja Bjorkquist. Minn., Wis., 1947-1955; 10 items (Reel 19)
  - Oiva Kujala
    - from: K. Kujala
      - Detroit, Mich., Marquette, Mich., 1960-1961; 3 items (Reel 19)
      - N.J., 1962; 1 items (Reel 19)
      - Detroit, Mich., 1962; 2 items (Reel 19)
      - Calif., 1964; 1 items (Reel 19)
  - Lyydia Lahtinen